asiacup2018live.info 2018-11-23

# Privacy Policy | Asia Cup 2018 Live Streaming

**asiacup2018live** is strongly committed to safeguarding its rights of privacy and its personal information. In order to earn our trust and confidence in our commitment, we are fully disclosing our privacy practices. We encourage you to understand what kind of personal identifying information we collect and how we use this information. **asiacup2018live** has the right to amend its privacy policy to suit the needs of the website and we will be able to update the latest issues at the earliest possible time.

The personal data collected on this site, notably through electronic subscription forms, are for the exclusive use of **asiacup2018live.info** , to the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, and cannot be disclosed or sold to third parties. The users of this site have the rights of access, opposition and correction of the data they have disclosed. As a result, user’s personal data can be corrected, completed, updated or erased if required to the **asiacup2018live.info** commercial service.asiacup2018live.info makes reasonable efforts to implement technology and security features in order to safeguard the privacy of its users from loss, unauthorized access or improper use.asiacup2018live.info may store your information in its databases, such as a Customer Relationship database, for reference. The information may be retained and used by asiacup2018live.info for a reasonable period, reflecting our need to answer queries or resolve problems, provide improved and new services and any data retention requirements of the law. This means we may retain information after an individual has ceased interacting with us. asiacup2018live.info does not sell, rent or give your personal data to any third party except where the law permits or unless you specifically agree.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

**asiacup2018** has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: asbarali@live.com
